# Mrudu Lahari Malayanur

Mrudu-lahari.Portfolio | LinkedIn | Email: mrudulahari.m@gmail.com | Mobile: +91-6383965677

### SALESFORCE DEVELOPER

Passionate Full-Stack Developer with over **1.5 years of experience** in **Salesforce development**. I posses strong analytical and problem-solving skills along with an ability to work independently or as part of a team. I have extensive experience in creating custom unique responsive user interfaces using **lightning Web Framework**, **HTML/CSS**, **Java**, **JavaScript**, **SOQL-Salesforce and REST API Integrations** with a focus to participate in research related to exploring new findings and developments in the field of human-computer interactions to improve user experience.

#### **EDUCATION**

## Vellore Institute of Technology - Bachelor's of Technology

Bachelor of Electronics and Communication Engineering CGPA: 8.65/10.00

July 2018 - July 2022 Vellore, India

Location: India

**Program Core / Program Electives:** Computer Communications, Digital Logic Design, Digital Signal Processing, VLSI System Design, Digital Communication Systems, Microcontroller and its applications, Robotics and Automation.

**University Electives:** Problem Solving and Object Oriented Programming, Problem Solving with Data Structures and Algorithms, Microcontroller and its Applications, Sensors and Instrumentation, Introduction to Business Communication, Advanced JAVA Programming, IoT Domain Analyst.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Associate Salesforce Developer**

Bajaj Finserv Health Limited

June 2022 - Present *Pune, India* 

- Designed and developed dynamic and responsive custom websites using **Lightning Web Components Framework** (LWC-Salesforce), JavaScript, SOQL, VisualForce pages.
- Worked with **REST APIs** to retrieve and display data from databases to integrat inter-departmental Functionalities.
- Optimized **website performance** and speed through Decommissioning custom object on Bajaj operational sales flow by **24%**.
- Lead the development and implementation of customized Product catalog handlers and lead Owner Allocations developed using **workflows**, **process builders and triggers** to **automate** lead owner allocations based on selection criteria.

## **CO-OP Internship- Capstone Project**

Bajaj Finserv Health Limited

Jan 2022 - June 2022 Pune, India

- Worked with **Lightning Web Framework** to develop robust and scalable interfaces.
- Debug and fix production bugs on high priority for smooth operation of the Salesforce community portal.
- Develop custom user journey Data interactions LeadManagerV3 **API integrations** on custom end-to-end Sales Journey to create leads and flow through opportunity closure.
- Implemented **security and data protection** based on different hierarchy levels.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Languages : JavaScript, SQL, Java, HTML, CSS, Apex - Salesforce, Python.

**Frameworks** : React js, Lightning Web Components - Salesforce.

**Databases** : MySQL.

**Dev Tools** : Visual Studio Code, Intelli JIDEA, Git.

**Softwares** : Salesforce, Figma, Canva, Microsoft word, Excel, Power Point.

#### **SPAST International Conference:**

**HRI (Human-Robot Interaction):** Naidu, Sai Vinay, Mrudu Lahari M, and Sujatha R. 2021. "HRI (Human-Robot Interaction) Using Machine Learning Based Automatic Gesture Recognition With KLT Tracker". SPAST Abstracts 1 (01). https://spast.org/techrep/article/view/656.

## **PROJECTS**

## **UI-UX design of Restuarant Website**

- \* HTML, CSS, Advanced CSS, Git.
- \* Designed and developed a clean and modern website using advanced CSS.
- \* Utilized responsive design to ensure compatibility across all devices.
- \* Deployed on GitHub pages via GitHub Actions.

# **UI-UX design representation of Netflix Landing page**

- \* Languages Used: HTML, CSS, and Advanced CSS.
- \* An End-End responsive design interpretation and development, of Netflix Landing page.
- \* Interpretation of UI performed using Figma.

# **Smart Car Parking System**

- \* Tools and languages Used: Proteus, Keil, Microcontroller 8051, ASM language.
- \* Smart Car parking system is designed to detect the free parking slots.
- \* MICRO 8051 interpreted by ASM language and sensor systems activated based on free slot systems.

# **CERTIFICATONS**

- Salesforce Platform Developer-1.
- Salesforce Certified Administrator.
- Introduction to JavaScript, Microsoft Technology Associate.
- Domain Specialist conforming to National Skill Qualifications Framework Level 8, NASSCOM IoT.

#### LEADERSHIP AND INVOLVEMENT

- Head of Editorial at IEEE Technology and Engineering Management Society, VIT University for the academic tenure of 2021 2022.
- Lead content writer at IEEE Technology and Engineering Management Society, VIT University for the academic tenure of 2018 2021.